<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The server that runs on Bitcoin!</title>
    <description>Bitquest is a &quot;Survival&quot; style Minecraft server with a Bitcoin-denominated economy: Players can buy, sell and trade items using BTC micropayments with a fully funcional Bitcoin wallet you can send money to/from. To start playing, Connect to the following address using the PC Version of Minecraft: play.bitquest.co
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 14:39:20 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 14:39:20 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to BitQuest 2.0</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hDK3kMb.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Santa has come to Satoshi Town with a special surprise!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to announce that &lt;strong&gt;BitQuest is now available as an open source Minecraft Spigot Plugin&lt;/strong&gt;. The first plugin ever to integrate Bitcoin as an in-game currency. You can check the official repository here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitquest/bitquest&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bitquest/bitquest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitQuest started as a side project by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/explodi&quot;&gt;explodi&lt;/a&gt; to create an unique Minecraft server with a Bitcoin-denominated economy, where players could buy, sell and trade items using BTC micropayments. One year later, we had quite a run: &lt;strong&gt;324 commits, and more than 6 BTC earned by players&lt;/strong&gt;, and we want to take it further, which is why we want to make more people be involved with the development. We put extra effort to clean up the code to open source BitQuest as a Minecraft Spigot plugin, all with a MIT license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means you can run your own BitQuest server with a Bitcoin wallet of your choice as the main reserve, and build Minecraft realms fuelled with the power of Bitcoin as an in-game economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few points we want to clarify for our current (and new) players:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will be still be hosting the main BitQuest server where you can check the shiny new features. But now there will be two servers: “The Classic” (&lt;strong&gt;play.bitquest.co&lt;/strong&gt;), the actual server, and the “The Beta” (&lt;strong&gt;beta.bitquest.co&lt;/strong&gt;) who runs the last version. We encourage everyone to play the beta server and give us feedback about bugs or new features you would love to see.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The gameplay have been streamlined, &lt;strong&gt;Banks and emerald blocks have been deprecated&lt;/strong&gt;. Players get BTC loot directly (through blockchain transactions) from killing mobs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can register your own terrain to avoid griefing to your buildings placing a sign with the name of the area, this will cost you 20 bits, and you can expand the terrain placing adjacent signs with the same name.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Next year, we’ll be deprecating the classic server in favour of the last version. We haven’t any schedule for this, but we’ll be notifying before it happens to our players through the BitQuest Chronicle Newsletter and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/bitquest&quot;&gt;subreddit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also making public the BitQuest site through Github Pages. If you’re a web developer and want to contribute to our current site, feel free too fork our Jekyll repository: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitquest/bitquest.github.io&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bitquest/bitquest.github.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to thank &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Xeyler&quot;&gt;Xeyler&lt;/a&gt;, the BitQuest Slack and &lt;a href=&quot;http://mego.cl&quot;&gt;Mego&lt;/a&gt; for helping on this huge re-launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re hoping to see you on the brand new BitQuest.
Merry Christmas!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 17:17:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/12/21/welcome-to-the-bitquest-2.0.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/12/21/welcome-to-the-bitquest-2.0.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BitQuest 2.0 is coming soon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi fellow BitQuesters!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve been quiet for a period of a few months, and we are deeply sorry for all of you guys who felt abandoned, but the time has come to re structure this project and find the best way to achieve the great ideas we have for this server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past 2 months we’ve been writing the server code from scratch, which was a arduous task to implement a new design. We all know that BitQuest 1.0 had a lot of bugs and problems with Bitcoin and most of the problems originate due to the very fact that the Minecraft engine is not designed to handle any type of in-game currency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the past year we have come up with a strategy to make the server a lot more stable and easier to mantain, however, this new design requires completely different technology and the need to rewrite most of the code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also learnt that there is a lot of people who want to support the project via donations, code contributions and lending free servers and we think the best vehicle to allow contibutions, transparency and resillience to the project is to make it open source. That way the contributions will help not only make BitQuest the best Minecraft server in the world, also allowing other people to make their own BitQuests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From now on, all the game code resides on &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/bitquest/bitquest&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, so we can all keep track of the development process and (more importantly) get involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe Bitcoin is gonna be the official currency of virtual worlds, hands down. And while still in its infancy, this is the time to experiment integrating this new technology and keeping BitQuest closed is not a cool way to contribute to the Bitcoin community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, My main task will be to help new developers get started by documenting the code and tools, creating spaces for discussion of the future of the project and keeping a transparent, organized, democratic organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, my company (&lt;a href=&quot;http://mego.cl&quot;&gt;MEGO&lt;/a&gt;) will be sponsoring this project with production, testing and development servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited for the future of this project, but it will come faster and greater with a bigger team. If you want to join the moderators or dev team, please drop me a line at cristian@mego.cl&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for playing!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 17:17:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/12/07/starting-bitquest-2.0.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/12/07/starting-bitquest-2.0.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
